我们能给任何人的最好的礼物
the greatest gift we can give anyone
不是珠宝
is not jewelry
、鲜花
or flowers
或新的 macbook pro
or a new macbook pro
，而是简单地将
it is to simply give
我们的注意力给予某人
our attention to someone
我们全部的
our full
complete
100 次
关注，
attention
这是为了让其他
this is to allow someone else
人成为你的一部分，
to become a part of you
让
to allow
他们的空间
their space
to be
没有 判断
without judgment
或标签，
or labels
但在完全
but with total
接受的情况下，这
acceptance this
就是真正的治疗
is what true healing is all about
在一个
in a world of
注意力不足
attention deficit
和不断分心的世界里，
and constant distractions
只和
it's even more valuable to just be with
一个
someone
你不必
you don't have to say
说正确的话的人在一起更有价值
the right thing
只是花时间和某人在一起
simply spending time with someone
[音乐 ]
[Music]
是你能做的最美妙的事情
is the most wonderful thing you can do
，这就是为什么他们称之为关注
that's why they call it pay attention
和花时间，
and spend time
因为它比任何礼物都更无价
because it's more priceless than any
gift
[音乐]
[Music]
the act
of
分享那个空间的行为
sharing that space
将手放在他们的手上
putting a hand on their hand
[音乐]
[Music]
to embrace in a hug
拥抱 让你的两颗心
and allow your two hearts
彼此相距不到一英寸，
to get within an inch of each other
and to
找到
find that
一致的跳动，
beat in unison
并
and to breathe
以自然发生的相同模式呼吸，
in the same pattern as naturally happens
我们可以给予
we can give love and healing
每一个人爱和治愈 我们是一个神秘的
each and every one of us is a mystical
治疗师，
healer
我们每个人
we each
都可以为彼此做这件事，
can do this for each other
只是那种无私的温暖拥抱
it's simply that warm hug
that is just selfless
，你只是把你的能量转移
and you're just transferring your energy
给那个人
to that person
[音乐]
[Music]
，你只是
and you're just saying
用你的身体
with your body
和能量说
and energy
i
我在
am
这里 对你来说，
here for you
这是最伟大的爱的行为有
this is the greatest act of love there
is
多少
how many
世界领导人
world leaders
和独裁者
and dictators
只是在
are simply
表现出来，
acting out
因为他们缺乏
because they lacked
温暖
warmth
、触摸和爱
and touch and love
[音乐]
[Music]
我们的身体和
the heat our bodies and
手发出的热量
hands give off
是我们自己的能量
is our own energy
有能量
there is an energy
汇聚这 这是真实的，
convergence this is real
这就是
this is what energy is
that radiating
能量，热、光和爱的辐射能量
energy of heat and light and love
，
that can be felt
可以通过触摸的行为感受到
simply through the act of touch
，看着某人的眼睛
to look into someone's eyes
，
and to
让光子
have photons firing back and forth
在彼此之间来回发射
between each other
[音乐]，
[Music]
同时
simultaneously
连接到他们的大脑
connecting to their brain
and creating a vision of the other
person
在彼此的脑海中创造另一个人的愿景
in each other's mind
这就是
this is what happens
当我们与某人坐在一起时
when we sit with someone
we are taking them in
to our own mind and our own heart
and they
you
发生的事情
there is a merging that takes place
and
a oneness
it can be felt so greatly
and so powerfully
当我们与另一个人静静地坐在一起
as we sit in silence
with another person
，聆听
as we listen
他们需要说的任何事情，
to anything they need to say
然后他们对我们说时，我们会感受到这种合一的发生和合一
and they to us
[音乐]
[Music]
有一种佛教冥想
there's a buddhist meditation
，任何人都可以
which anyone can do
做 和别人坐在一起
where you sit with someone else
，你只是盯着他们的眼睛看了
and you just stare into their eyes
很长一段时间
for an extended period of time
，一开始感觉很尴尬和奇怪，
at first it feels awkward and weird and
你想把目光移开
you want to look away
，当你突破这一点时，
and as you break through this
会有一种强烈的感觉
there is a great sense
，即两者成为一个
of the two becoming one
自我消失了
ego dissolves
自私消失了
selfishness dissolves
并且有一种
and there is a sharing
分享仍然是
that remains
[音乐]
[Music]
一种强大的联系
a powerful connection
，它
that is
真正具有治愈性和变革性
truly healing and transformative
[音乐]
[Music]
in ways that
有时单独冥想永远做不到
sometimes meditating alone can never do
它对任何人来说都是一种强大的练习
it is a powerful practice for anyone
朋友
friends
亲戚
relatives
生活伴侣
life partners
just as
就像我们通常认为
when we normally think
我们认为的那样
we think one word at a time
一次一个词，当我们说话时，我们一次说一个词，
and when we speak we speak one word at a
time
但这种
but this form of
交流或自我交流
communication or self-communication
的形式非常有限，
is very limited
一次一个词不是很多
one word at a time is not a lot of
信息
information
但是当我们感觉到
but when we feel
时，当我们感觉到时，
when we sense
我们可以同时吸收
we can take in
成千上万的
thousands and millions of
感官知觉
sense perceptions
all at once
，我们可以调谐到这种
and we can tune into this
理解中，
understanding
这种更深刻的
this deeper
智慧
wisdom
，我们可以
and we can share this
与另一个人分享
with another person
，我们可以真正地与他们的灵魂交流
and we can truly commune with their soul
，真正地得到 他们存在的本质
and truly get an essence of their being
far more effectively
远比我们正常的交流方式更有效
than our normal mode of communication
，所以不要
and so do not be
害怕和某人坐在一起
afraid to sit with someone
不要害怕沉默
do not be afraid of silence
不要觉得需要总是填满它
do not feel the need to always fill it
因为只是为了某人在那里
because simply being there for someone
并与某人在一起
and being with someone
并且 给他们
and giving them
你所有的存在和他们你
all of your being and them you
是我们可以拥有的最强大的
is the most powerful
治愈
healing
和变革体验
and transformative experience
we can have
[音乐]
[Music]
你